[ whir! ]■
just for you...
steven!
[laughs]
It's talking to him?
It shouldn't be
able to do that.
I-it should only
be following orders.
Garnet, do something.
Steven.
[laughs]
Nooooo!
You should just
give us back the mirror.
It will be safer where
we can watch it.
Yeah, let's bubble it.
Nooooo!
[echoing]■
- Wha...
- Steven.
Don't make me have to
take it from you.
[ gasps ]
It doesn't want
to go with you.
Don't you hear
it screaming?
Steven,
it's just a mirror, a tool.
It can't want anything.
[echoing]■
Nooooo!
[echoing]
Nooooo! Nooooo!
Nooooo!
[ groans ]
It wants to be with me!
[ gasps ]
Aah! Aah! I'm sorry!
That little boy
is in big trouble.
Garnet, wait!
I'm sure he didn't
understand what he was doing!
Fan out.
[ breathing heavily ]
[ panting ]
[ sighs ]
What am I gonna do?
What's their
problem with you?
Are you trying
to say something?
[ warble! ]
Away from home.
Let...
me...
out!
I don't understand.
PEARL:
Steven!
Come on!
I want to help you!
What can I do?
[ whooshing, warbling ]
[ grunting ]
Ah!
[ gasps ]
Wha...
[ sighs ]
Thank you.
You didn't --
Ohh.
[ sighs ]
You actually
talked to me.
You helped me!
It's Steven, right?
[ breathes deeply ]
Mm.
I'm Lapis --
Lapis Lazuli.
Are you really
a Crystal Gem?
Yeah.
But you set me free.
But...wha...
Steven!
Wha...
Wait!
[ sternly ]
You...
[ gasps ]
[ sternly ]
You...
Did you even wonder
who I used to be?!
[ both grunt ]
Steven, run!
What are you doing?
I'm Lapis Lazuli, and you can't
keep me trapped here anymore!
Huh?
They're not
gonna let us leave.
Leave?
Steven, come with me.
Where?
Home.
B-b-but -- b-but I,
uh...
Fine.
[ grunting ]
[ breathing heavily ]
Don't trust them, Steven.
Goodbye.
[ both grunt ]
[ coughing, gagging ]
Steven! Are you okay?!
Yeah. I'm fine.
So, that was another Gem?
[ sighs ]
Yes.
GARNET:
Steven, you're grounded.
I'm grounded?
Yes, you're grounded.
You disobeyed an order.
Now we're gonna bury you till
you've learned your lesson.
Aah!
That's not how
grounding works!
[ door opens ]
STEVEN: Dad?
[ breathing heavily ]
Uh, you guys better
come check this out.
W-w-wha?
[ crowd murmuring ]
Wait.
What the...
Where did it go?
Whoa!
The ocean!
Huh?
Hey, it's those
magical ladies!
What's going on here?
The ocean is gone,
obviously.
That's right.
Now it's just a desert.
No one wants to take a
vacation to ...desert city!
Aw, we're gonna lose
all our summer business!
And all the
beach babes. Aw!
Who's gonna
buy my fries?
And my pizza!
Who's gonna have
fun at funland?
As Mayor, I demand you
explain this immediately!
It was Lapis Lazuli.
Lapis Lazuli?
She's the Gem you
released from the mirror.
[ crowd murmurs ]
That's incredible.
How did you do that?
But she's a Gem,
just like us.
There's a lot you don't
know about Gems, Steven.
How could I have
known the Gem
contained in that mirror
would be so powerful?
Where are you going,
Steven?
I'm leaving to fix
what I did to our home.