♪ TOOK A LOT OF TURNS ♪
♪ THAT TURNED OUT WRONG ♪
♪ THAT'S A WORN-OUT SONG ♪
♪ DAY BY DAY,
MOMENT BY MOMENT ♪
♪ TAKIN' MY CHANCES ♪
♪ TRUSTIN' MY HEART ♪
♪ IT WASN'T TOO SMART ♪
♪ I WILL SURVIVE,
I WILL ENDURE ♪
♪ WHEN THE GOING'S ROUGH,
YOU CAN BE SURE ♪
♪ I'LL TOUGH IT OUT,
I WON'T GIVE IN ♪
♪ IF I'M KNOCKED DOWN,
I'LL GET UP AGAIN ♪
♪ AS LONG AS MY DREAM'S ALIVE ♪
♪ I WILL SURVIVE ♪
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON NOW.
"Z"...
"E"...
OKAY.
"R"...
"O."
THAT'S IT.
I CAN HELP YOU DIG YOUR HOLE
SO YOU WON'T BE SO TIRED
TO TEACH ME.
NO, I'M FINE.
LOOK --
YOU'RE A SLOW DIGGER.
OH HO HO.
YOU'RE TRYING TO
BAG ON ME.
YEAH, I'M TRYING
TO BAG ON YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
THIS WAY, WE'LL BE DONE
AT THE SAME TIME.
WELL, IT COULDN'T HURT.
YEAH.
GO AHEAD.
"Z"...
"E"...
NO.
THIS HAS TO GO OUT
LIKE THIS.
THAT'S AN "R."
OKAY?
OKAY.
THIS ONE'S EASY.
"O."
THAT'S IT.
YOU KNOW, ZERO'S NOT
MY REAL NAME.
IT'S NOT?
BUT EVEN PENDANSKI
CALLS YOU "ZERO."
MY NAME'S HECTOR,
HECTOR ZERONI.
NICE TO MEET YOU, HECTOR.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
26 LETTERS.
SO WE CAN DO FIVE LETTERS
A DAY FOR FOUR DAYS,
AND THEN SIX LETTERS
ON THE FIFTH DAY.
THAT'S GOOD MATH.
I'M NOT STUPID.
I KNOW EVERYONE THINKS I AM.
I JUST DON'T LIKE ANSWERING
STUPID QUESTIONS.
RIGHT.
YO, CAVEMAN, IT MUST
BE KIND OF EASY
WORKING WITH YOUR OWN PERSONAL
SLAVE AND ALL, HUH?
WHAT'S UP, STUPID?
COME ON, SQUID.
WHATEVER, MAN.
"M"...
"O"...
"M."
WE WEREN'T ALWAYS HOMELESS.
I REMEMBER WE USED
TO LIVE IN A LOT
OF DIFFERENT PLACES.
AND THEN...
WE DIDN'T LIVE ANYWHERE.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN HARD.
YEAH.
MY MA HAD PROBLEMS,
BUT SHE WOULD TRY SO HARD TO
MAKE A BETTER LIFE FOR US.
YEAH.
SHE ALWAYS USED TO SAY,
"I LOVE YOU MORE THAN AIR."
SHE COULDN'T TAKE ME
EVERYWHERE SHE WENT.
I USED TO HAVE TO WAIT LIKE
ON A PORCH OR A PLAYGROUND.
[ SIGHS ]
THEN ONE DAY,
SHE DIDN'T COME BACK.
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER?
[ SIGHS DEEPLY ]
I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT BOTHERS ME
THE MOST.
IF I COULD,
I WOULD HIRE A WHOLE TEAM
OF PRIVATE INVESTIGATORS
JUST TO FIND HER...
OR TO FIND OUT
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER.
[ SIGHS ]
I USED TO WAIT
AT LANEY PARK.
LANEY PARK?
YEAH.
I USED TO GO TO LANEY PARK
ALL THE TIME.
OH, REALLY?
YEAH.
I USED TO SLEEP
IN THE TUNNEL NEXT
TO THE SWINGING BRIDGE.
BUT NO BIGGIE.
[ SIGHS ]
Dr. Pendanski:
LET'S GO, BOYS! LUNCH!
WHERE'S YOUR WHIP, CAVEMAN?
YOU DON'T WANT YOUR SLAVE
TO BE SLACKING OFF.
IT'S NOT SLAVERY.
IT'S AN AGREEMENT.
YEAH, MAN, WHATEVER.
LINE 'EM UP.
I DON'T HAVE ALL DAY.
LET'S GO. LET'S GO.
WE HAVE BOLOGNA AND CHEESE,
APPLES, AND GRAHAM CRACKERS.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S MOVE IT ALONG.
GET YOUR SANDWICH.
HELLO, THEODORE.
THAT'S NOT MY NAME, FOOL.
IT'S ARMPIT.
UH-HUH. ALAN,
A GOOD DAY TO YOU.
GOOD AFTERNOON.
RICKY...
SIR.
...SANDWICHES?
YOU CAN HAVE ONE SANDWICH.
[ MAGNET SPEAKING SPANISH ]
THIS IS AMERICA.
WE SPEAK ENGLISH HERE.
HEY, MAN, I GOT SOME
EXTRA GRAHAM CRACKERS.
HEY, HOW ABOUT
I GIVE YOU MY COOKIE
AND YOU LET ME
DIG YOUR HOLE?
GO ON. TAKE IT.
LOOK, I GET IT, ALL RIGHT?
I'LL DIG MY OWN HOLE
FROM NOW ON.
JUST LET ME EAT MY LUNCH.
[ Laughing ]
HE ISN'T GONNA TAKE IT.
COME HERE.
EAT THE COOKIE.
WHOA.
BACK OFF, MAN.
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
NOTHING, MOM.
WE WAS JUST FOOLING,
RIGHT?
I SAW WHAT WAS GOING ON.
GO ON, STANLEY.
TEACH HIM A LESSON.
HIT HIM BACK.
YEAH, TEACH ME A LESSON.
YEAH, STANLEY,
TEACH HIM A LESSON.
COME ON. HIT ME.
HIT HIM.
COME ON.
TEACH ME A LESSON.
HIT HIM, STANLEY.
[ BOYS MURMURING ]
GET HIM!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
UGH!
GO GET HIM.
THAT'S ENOUGH!
[ GRUNTING ]
I SAID, "THAT'S ENOUGH!"
THAT'S ENOUGH!
[ CHOKING ]
STOP. HEY, STOP, ZERO.
HEY, STOP.
COME ON, MAN.
[ CHOKING ]
[ GUNSHOT ]
NOW, I SAID, "THAT'S ENOUGH!"
WHEN I SAY TO END SOMETHING,
I MEAN END IT.
COME ON. LET'S GO.
GET BACK TO YOUR HOLES!
YOU ALL RIGHT?
ZERO'S CRAZY.
NO, NO, NO.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
(man)
My dad and I have the same eyes.
Same nose.
Same toughness.
And since he's had
moderate Alzheimer's disease,
the same never quit attitude.
That's why I asked his doctor
about once-a-day NAMZARIC.
(AVO)
NAMZARIC is approved
for moderate to severe
Alzheimer's disease in patients
who are taking donepezil.
It may improve cognition
and overall function,
and may slow the worsening
of symptoms for a while.
NAMZARIC does not change
the underlying
disease progression.
Don't take if allergic to
memantine, donepezil, piperidine
or any of the ingredients
in NAMZARIC.
Tell the doctor
about any conditions
including heart, lung, bladder,
kidney or liver problems,
seizures, stomach ulcers,
or procedures with anesthesia.
Serious side effects may occur,
including muscle problems
if given anesthesia;
slow heartbeat, fainting,
more stomach acid
which may lead
to ulcers and bleeding;
nausea, vomiting,
difficulty urinating,
seizures, and worsening
of lung problems.
Most common side effects are
headache, diarrhea, dizziness
loss of appetite, and bruising.
(man)
Dad and I shared
a lot of moments.
Now we're making the most
of each one.
(AVO)
Ask about NAMZARIC today.
Honey, aren't we having friends
over? It reeks in here.
I know [goat noise]
I stole the other team's mascot
for good luck.
We need to wash this room.
Wash it?
Yeah, wash it with Febreze.
For all the things
you can't wash,
use Febreze Fabric
Refresher
Wow
[inhales] it really
smells great in here.
DOG BARKS
And try pluggable Febreze,
with up to 4 times the
freshness in one refill.
Pluggable Febreze and
Fabric Refresher
[inhale + exhale mnemonic], two
more ways to breathe happy