>>> I'M LEAH GABRIELLE.
FIGHTERS ARE REPORTING DOZENS OF
AIR STRIKES HAPPENING IN THE
EASTERN PART OF ALEPPO.
THIS COMES A DAY AFTER TURKEY
AND RUSSIA WORKED OUT A
CEASE-FIRE MEANT TO HELP GET
REBELS AND CIVILIANS OUT OF
HARM'S WAY.
THE GOVERNMENT FORCES WITH HELP
FROM THE RUSSIAN MILITARY ARE
NOW CLOSE TO TAKING BACK THE
ENTIRE CITY FROM THE REBELS.
IN FACT, THE RUSSIANS REPORT THE
REBELS HAVE LESS THAN EIGHT
SQUARE MILES.
THE U.N. ESTIMATES 50,000 PEOPLE
ARE STILL TRAPPED IN ALEPPO.
YOU CAN SEE SOME HERE TRYING TO
MAKE THEIR WAY THROUGH THE
STREETS.
THE U.N. SECRETARY GENERAL SAYS
HE'S HEARD CREDIBLE REPORTS THAT
PRO-GOVERNMENT TROOPS ARE
MURDERING CIVILIANS AS THEY MOVE
THROUGH THE AREA.
AND A U.N. COMMISSION SAYS IT
LEARNED OF TROOPS ACCUSING
PEOPLE OF CRIMES AND CARRYING
OUT DEATHS ON THE SPOT.
THE NEWS CONTINUES WITH SHEP
RIGHT AFTER THIS.
>>> TOPPING THE NEWS, DONALD
TRUMP HAS RIPPED INTO THE U.N.
SAYS IT'S NO FRIEND OF THE
UNITED STATES.
HE CALLED IT A POLITICAL GAME
AND QUESTIONED WHETHER IT'S
WORTH THE MONEY WE'RE SPENDING.
THE U.N.'S INCOMING LEADER IS
LOOKING TO ADDRESS SOME OF
DONALD TRUMP'S CONCERNS.
EARLIER THIS WEEK THE FORMER
PORTUGUESE PRIME MINISTER
ANTONIO GUTIERREZ TOOK THE OATH
OF OFFICE TO BECOME THE NEXT
LEADER OF THE U.N.
HE'S PROMISING TO MAKE THE
ORGANIZATION MORE EFFICIENT
THROUGH MANAGEMENT REFORM.
DIPLOMATS ARE ALSO TELLING "THE
NEW YORK TIMES" NEWSPAPER THE
INCOMING SECRETARY GENERAL HAS
ALSO CHANGED HIS APPROACH TO
NEARLY EVERY MAJOR CRISIS AFTER
TRUMP'S ELECTION WIN.
ERIC SHAWN IS LIVE IN THE NEW
YORK CITY NEWSROOM.
HEY, ERIC.
>> SHEP, HE'S COMPLAINED ABOUT
OVERSPENDING BY DEFENSE
CONTRACTORS.
AND NEXT THE U.N. COULD FEEL THE
TRUMP PINCH.
THE PRESIDENT-ELECT'S VIEWS ARE
AT ODDS WITH THE WORLD BODY IN A
VARIETY OF PRESSING ISSUES, FROM
THE SUPPORT OF THE IRANIAN
NUCLEAR DEAL TO CLIMATE CHANGE
AND THE BUDGET COULD SOON BE ON
THE LINE ALSO.
FORMER U.N. AMBASSADOR JOHN
BOLTON SERVED WITH GEORGE W.
BUSH AND TALKED TO THE PRESIDENT
ABOUT JOINING THE
ADMINISTRATION.
CRITICS THINK THE
PRESIDENT-ELECT WILL TAKE A HARD
STANCE AT THE U.N.
HE SAYS THE ALMOST $3 BILLION IN
AMERICAN TAXPAYERS THIS YEAR
ALONE, THE MOST OF ANY OF THE
NATION, COULD FACE CUTS.
>> I THINK A GOOD, HARD LOOK AT
THE U.N. BUDGET IS LONG OVERDUE.
AND I WOULDN'T BE AT ALL
SURPRISED IF A PRESIDENT TRUMP
WANTS AN OFFICE THAT WILL PAY
ATTENTION TO HIM.
>> DONALD TRUMP TESTIFIED TO
CONGRESS, AT LEAST IN A
DISCUSSION NEAR THE
MULTI-BILLION RENOVATION BACK IN
2006.
WHEN HE ATTACKED THE U.N. THEN
OF OVERSPENDING.
>> IT IS THE MOST CORRUPT THING
GOING ON IN THE WORLD, WHICH IS
SAYING SOMETHING, OR ONE OF THE
MOST INCOMPETENT THINGS I'VE
EVER SEEN.
>> HE SOUNDS VERY SIMILAR TODAY.
MR. TRUMP ASKED NIKKI HAILEY FOR
U.S. AMBASSADOR.
AND A POSSIBLE PREVIEW WHAT SHE
COULD FACE IF SHE TAKES THE JOB
IF SHE'S ACCEPTED BY THE SENATE.
HE SAID, WELL, IN A QUOTE, HE
SAID, THEY WERE POPULISTS,
DEMAGOGUES AND FEDERAL CHIEFS.
HE COMPARED THEIR LANGUAGE TO
THE POP BEGAN DAY OF ISIS.
>> ERIC SHAWN LIVE IN NEW YORK
CITY, THANK YOU.
>>> AND THERE'S BREAKING NEWS ON
FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
WE HAVE JUST GOTTEN WORD FROM A
SYRIAN REBEL TRUCE DEAL.
WITHIN HOURS, WE ARE HOPING IT
WILL SAVE TENS OF THOUSANDS OF
LIVES.
>>> THE CITY IS UNDER SIEGE FOR
YEARS.
HUNDREDS OF SYRIANS HAVE DIED
THIS THE CIVIL WAR.
NOW IT APPEARS THAT MOST OF THE
CITY WAS TAKEN BACK FROM THE
REBELS IN ALEPPO.
AND NOW TENS OF THOUSANDS OF
CIVILIANS ARE TRAP IN A
ONE-MILE-SQUARE AREA OF BURNED
OUT AND BOMBED OUT REMNANTS OF A
PREVIOUS GREAT CITY IN THE
WORLD.
AND ARE NOW TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
IF THEY WILL ALL BE LINED UP OR
BE ALLOWED TO ESCAPE.
THERE WAS A BRIEF CEASE-FIRE
IMPLEMENTED OVER A PERIOD OF
HOURS.
BY THE THOUSANDS, THEY LINED UP
FOR BUSES THAT WE'LL TAKE PEOPLE
TO A SAFE AREA.
THEY BEGAN TO WORK ON AN
AGREEMENT TO TRY TO GET THE
SURVIVORS WITH THEIR CHILDREN
AND EVERYTHING THEY OWN ON THEIR
BACKS OUT OF THIS CITY OF
ALEPPO.
WELL, NOW THE WORD HAS JUST COME
TO THE RUSE SERVICE.
THE TRUTH'S DEAL IS COING AND
BEING BOMBARDED.
WE'LL KEEP YOU UPGRADED.
>>> AND MANY ARE TRYING TO CASH
IN ON PRESIDENT-ELECT'S TWEET.
LAST WEEK HE LAUNCHED A TWITTER
TIRADE OVER THE BUILDING OF THE
NEW AIR FORCE ONE.
EVEN OFFERING HIM ANY ADVICE ON
THE F-35 PROGRAM.
>>> SOME TRADERS ARE NOW
UPDATING THEIR COMPUTER MODELS
TO TRY TO PROFIT WHEN TRUMP
TWEETS ABOUT COMPANIES.
IN OTHER WORDS, IF HE SAYS
SOMETHING BAD ABOUT THE ECONOMY,
YOU WANT TO GET IN ON THE DOWN
AND CASH UP.
THE VOTES DO SEEM TO HAPPEN.
THE MORE TWEETS, THE BETTER THE
PROMS REMAKE.
>>> AND WE ARE DEALING WITH A
PRESIDENT WHO TWEETS, BUT THAT
IS NEW FOR TRADERS.
>> Reporter: IT IS A TOTALLY NEW
WORLD.
IF YOU THINK ABOUT THE TRUMP
REPORTERS OUTSIDE OF TRUMP
TOWER, AT 8:26 MONDAY, AN HOUR
BEFORE THE OPENING BELL, THE
COST IS TWEETED THE
PRESIDENT-ELECT SAYS THE F-35
PROGRAM AND COST IS OUT OF
CONTROL.
SO WITH THE TWEET, YOU TAKE THAT
OFF, IT'S ABOUT $4 BILLION, GIVE
OR TAKE, FROM THE COMPANY'S
STOCK MARKET VALUE IN JUST A FEW
HOURS.
BUT LEN TO WHAT WE DO OVER AND
OVER AGAIN.
>> I WORK WITH A REGULATED
SECURITIES INDUSTRY WHERE I
THINK TEN YEARS AGO IT WOULD VM
BEEN A HER SEE TO HAVE MUCH A
WONDERFUL DAY ON TWITTER.
SOCIAL MEDIA, WHAT IS THAT?
WELL, THE PRESIDENT IS GOING TO
ADOPT TO SOCIAL ISSUES.
AND THERE IS SOME GRAY AREA.
MR. TRUMP SAID H